Russian leaders in the region have confirmed that one has withdrawn -
- Of what you describe as tactical reasons.
From robotyne, one spreads in both eastern and western direction, towards Verbove -
- Which is located nearby to move on to the next Russian line of defense.
This is an important step, maybe a breakthrough.
The goal is set to inta or isolate the strategically important city of Tokmak -
- Cirka ten kilometers south of Robotyne.
In these battles, it now seems that the Ukrainians have takeover with artillery -
- That you shot a lot of the Russian.
It is one of the most important factors in this battle.
Heavy drone attacks have been directed at Ukrainian port cities -
- Several nights in a row, during the week.
Russia, since they withdrew from the grain agreement a month ago -
–Have invested a lot in trying to knock out the Ukrainian economy -
–And
Cereal exports, which is a large source of income for Ukraine.
The attacks against the cities of Izmail and Reni attracted considerable attention -
- As the cities are located right on the border with Natoland Romania.
And the countries had different views on what really happened.
The drone attacks performed by the Russian Federation -
- No direct threat to our national territory.
I.a.
Should you have paid SEK 210 million for winter jackets that cannot withstand cold.
You have also bought food for the army for three times as high as normal.
That there is corruption in Ukraine, it is well known, but it is also well known -
- That you have an extensive endeavor to fight this corruption.
This week, one of the country's richest businessmen for money laundering - was charged
- And several high -ranking officials have been allowed to resign after corruption charges.
Most recently the country's defense minister Oleksij Reznikov.
Although Reznikov personally has not been accused of something -
- So Ukraine's Ministry of Defense has been affected by several corruption scandals.
Oleksij Reznikov has lived through more than 550 days of full -scale war.
I think the ministry needs new approaches -
It includes control and audit -
- That can be implemented together with the Ukrainian authorities.
They are also keen on this.
Former Defense Minister Reznikov-
- Have talked about having to be open with how this works.
I don't think we should be worried, but we should be vigilant -
–And we will help Ukraine collectively to overcome corruption.
In mid-September, the first Abrams tanks are expected from the USA-
- Delivered to Ukraine.
It states sources for Politico, who say -
- The first delivery of ten tanks is currently in Germany.
Something that has attracted attention is that the tanks may be delivered -
- Together with ammunition containing depleted uranium.
When using uranium, you take some of the uranium and enrich it for nuclear power plants.
That which is the residual product, with low radiation-
- Is just a very heavy and dense metal and with it you make alloys -
- To the arrow projectile, as the United Kingdom, which the United States has - as Russia has.
That which can form a danger with radioactivity -
- It is precisely at the impact, that gases and small splits are formed.
They are dangerous, especially for the crew of the vehicle hit -
- But they probably have other problems to think about when they are met.
North Korea's leader Kim Jong-Un is expected to visit Russia and Vladimir Putin-
- In September, there are sources for the US defense ministry.
Russia has very few friends left and North Korea is one of the countries -